[
    {
    "number": 1,
    "question": "Fear : Threat : : Anger : ?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Compulsion"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Panic"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Provocation"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Force"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "number": 2,
    "question": "Dove : Peace?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Crow : Scavenge"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Knife : Cut"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Lull : Storm"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Pearl : Purity"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "d"
},
{
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Happiness in related to Sorrow in the same way as Comfort is related to ________",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Hardship"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Rest"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Poverty"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Difficulty"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "a"
},
{
    "number": 4,
    "question": "Clock : Time :: Thermometer : ?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Heat"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Radiation"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Energy"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Temperature"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "d"
},
{
    "number": 5,
    "question": "Contamination : Food :: Infection : ?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Germs"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Disease"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Body"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Medicine"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "number": 6,
    "question": "Arm : Elbow : : Leg : ?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Toe"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Knee"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Thigh"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Ankle"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "d"
},
{
    "number": 7,
    "question": "Race: Fatigue :: Fast: ?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Food"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Appetite"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Hunger"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Weakness"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "number": 8,
    "question": "Inn : Traveller",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Lodging : Man"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Country : Citizen"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Dormitory : Students"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Ashram : Gurus"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "number": 9,
    "question": "ACE : FHJ : OQS : ?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "PRT"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "RTU"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "TVX"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "UWY"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
},
{
    "number": 10,
    "question": "Melt : Liquid : : Freeze : ?",
    "choices": [
        {
            "letter": "a",
            "label": "Ice"
        },
        {
            "letter": "b",
            "label": "Condense"
        },
        {
            "letter": "c",
            "label": "Solid"
        },
        {
            "letter": "d",
            "label": "Crystal"
        }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
}
]